thwglobal.com 2016-11-26

# Welcome to THW Global - Online Video Sharing Community

**Registered To Date**  
1,532,302

**Global Registrations Still Needed**  
3,467,698

**Demographic Profiles Completed**  
685,555

**PRIVACY POLICY**

Effective June 15, 2016 

Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and disclose and make use of personal information. The following outlines our privacy policy. 

If you register with us, we require certain personally identifiable information from you. We will collect and use personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law. We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned. Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date. We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification. 

**SECURITY** \- The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information on our order forms, such as credit card number, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. 

Because no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information yet cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our site, please contact us as indicated below. 

**OPTING OUT OF OUR INFORMATION SERVICES** \- We may occasionally send you information on special offers, promotions, or product updates, or you may be a subscriber to our newsletters or you may have opted in to receive newsletters or special promotions from one of our trusted third party providers. If you decide you no longer wish to receive these communications, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each newsletter or communication or by contacting the THWGlobal.com Customer Service Team with the email address below. 

**COOKIES** \- A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user's computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies to collect anonymous information about how you use this site by setting and accessing cookies on your computer. These cookies track information such as how often you visit our site, what pages you view, and where you go after you leave our site. The cookies are not connected to your personal information. 

**WEB BEACONS** \- "Web beacons" or clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of web users. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user's computer hard drive, web beacons are embedded invisibly on web pages and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. We utilize web beacons that help us better manage content on our site by informing us what content is effective. We do not tie the information gathered by web beacons to your personally identifiable information. 

**LINKS TO OTHER SITES** \- This site may contain links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by us. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites. This privacy statement applies only to information collected by this site. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. 

**CHILDREN UNDER 13** \- Children under 13 may view our site, but they cannot make a purchase, nor provide any personal information. Our site is not designed for children and we do not wish to collect personal information from children under 13. If you register with us and we discover that you are under 13, we will delete your registration. We will send you a message if we do this. 

**CHANGES TO PRIVACY** \- If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of the change. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. 

We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained. We will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information. 

If you have any questions regarding the use of our site or our Privacy Policy please contact us at: 

email: info@thwglobal.com

THW-PRIVACYPOLICY-V1.0 | Lasy Revised 06/15/2016
